[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "I'm doing great, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "doing", "great", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 24, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 25, "answer": "You've been keeping your head below the Parapet since the shellacking you guys took in the election.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "been", "keeping", "your", "head", "below", "the", "Parapet", "since", "the", "shellacking", "you", "guys", "took", "in", "the", "election", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 26, "question": "What is your reaction to the pretty poor defeat?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "the", "pretty", "poor", "defeat", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 27, "answer": "Well, I mean I think that we got to look at everything that we're doing.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", "I", "think", "that", "we", "got", "to", "look", "at", "everything", "that", "we", "'re", "doing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 33, "question": "With hindsight, was it a mistake to choose Mitt Romney as the Republican nominee?", "question_tokens": ["With", "hindsight", ",", "was", "it", "a", "mistake", "to", "choose", "Mitt", "Romney", "as", "the", "Republican", "nominee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 34, "answer": "No, I don't think so at all.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "Right, where is it?", "question_tokens": ["Right", ",", "where", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "-- pretty substantial spending cuts and tax increases.", "answer_tokens": ["--", "pretty", "substantial", "spending", "cuts", "and", "tax", "increases", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 124, "question": "Are you accusing the president of lying?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "accusing", "the", "president", "of", "lying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 125, "answer": "You've never seen this plan.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "'ve", "never", "seen", "this", "plan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Is he lying?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "lying", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "I don't think the plan is out there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "the", "plan", "is", "out", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "They're lying, are they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "lying", ",", "are", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "I'm not saying that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "saying", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Yes, but, Reince, if the plan is exactly as he has stated here, and it includes some tax increases as the vast majority, nearly two thirds, more than two thirds of the American public want, actually want, if that is on the table, why wouldn't the Republicans sign up to it?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "but", ",", "Reince", ",", "if", "the", "plan", "is", "exactly", "as", "he", "has", "stated", "here", ",", "and", "it", "includes", "some", "tax", "increases", "as", "the", "vast", "majority", ",", "nearly", "two", "thirds", ",", "more", "than", "two", "thirds", "of", "the", "American", "public", "want", ",", "actually", "want", ",", "if", "that", "is", "on", "the", "table", ",", "why", "would", "n't", "the", "Republicans", "sign", "up", "to", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", "CD", "NNS", ",", "RBR", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VB", ",", "RB", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "DT", "NNPS", "NN", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Listen, I don't know the details of what he's offering, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "the", "details", "of", "what", "he", "'s", "offering", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Senate"]}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", ":", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "What is your opinion of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "opinion", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "Well, I'm going to -- listen, and that's kind of things, Piers, national security, the decisions that have to be made in regard to the secretary of state, I'm going to leave that up to the leadership in our -- in our Senate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "--", "listen", ",", "and", "that", "'s", "kind", "of", "things", ",", "Piers", ",", "national", "security", ",", "the", "decisions", "that", "have", "to", "be", "made", "in", "regard", "to", "the", "secretary", "of", "state", ",", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "leave", "that", "up", "to", "the", "leadership", "in", "our", "--", "in", "our", "Senate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["2 percent"]}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NN", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNPS", ",", "CC", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Is the president going to hold his nerve and increase taxes or is he going to be bullied off by the Republicans to try and do a deal to avoid falling off the fiscal cliff?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "the", "president", "going", "to", "hold", "his", "nerve", "and", "increase", "taxes", "or", "is", "he", "going", "to", "be", "bullied", "off", "by", "the", "Republicans", "to", "try", "and", "do", "a", "deal", "to", "avoid", "falling", "off", "the", "fiscal", "cliff", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "The president has been quite clear that he wants a balanced approach to our deficit problems, that he wants higher revenue raised from increasing taxes for the top 2 percent, the most fortunate Americans, and spending cuts so that we are on a fiscally sustainable path.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "president", "has", "been", "quite", "clear", "that", "he", "wants", "a", "balanced", "approach", "to", "our", "deficit", "problems", ",", "that", "he", "wants", "higher", "revenue", "raised", "from", "increasing", "taxes", "for", "the", "top", "2", "percent", ",", "the", "most", "fortunate", "Americans", ",", "and", "spending", "cuts", "so", "that", "we", "are", "on", "a", "fiscally", "sustainable", "path", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "POS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "JJS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NNPS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "DT", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "What is plan B?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "plan", "B", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Well, first of all, I don't think that's in the country's best interest, and I think we've heard from Republicans that they are finally talking about raising revenue from upper income families, so these are solvable problems and we are doing our best to try to solve them.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "that", "'s", "in", "the", "country", "'s", "best", "interest", ",", "and", "I", "think", "we", "'ve", "heard", "from", "Republicans", "that", "they", "are", "finally", "talking", "about", "raising", "revenue", "from", "upper", "income", "families", ",", "so", "these", "are", "solvable", "problems", "and", "we", "are", "doing", "our", "best", "to", "try", "to", "solve", "them", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "But what do you feel about Grover Norquist and his implacable opposition to raising taxes which seems to have been the mantra for so many Republicans for so long?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "Grover", "Norquist", "and", "his", "implacable", "opposition", "to", "raising", "taxes", "which", "seems", "to", "have", "been", "the", "mantra", "for", "so", "many", "Republicans", "for", "so", "long", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNPS", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "No, I'm an economist and to me, the solution to our problems is quite clear.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "an", "economist", "and", "to", "me", ",", "the", "solution", "to", "our", "problems", "is", "quite", "clear", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Grover Norquist"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Does that make sense?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "make", "sense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "RBR", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Thirty- two million copies, Rick Warren?", "question_tokens": ["Thirty-", "two", "million", "copies", ",", "Rick", "Warren", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "CD", "CD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Yes, nobody is more surprised than I am.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "nobody", "is", "more", "surprised", "than", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Warren"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 355, "question": "I mean I'm assuming you would be in the wealthiest who should give away more, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "I", "'m", "assuming", "you", "would", "be", "in", "the", "wealthiest", "who", "should", "give", "away", "more", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "RBR", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 356, "answer": "Well, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "Am I right?", "question_tokens": ["Am", "I", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Yes, that's true.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "that", "'s", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Are they made gay?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "they", "made", "gay", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 534, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 535, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121127pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "And what would you -- what would you counsel him?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "would", "you", "--", "what", "would", "you", "counsel", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", ":", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Well, I don't really know his motivation behind it, so I would -- I would like to talk to him first before I would comment on his issue.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "really", "know", "his", "motivation", "behind", "it", ",", "so", "I", "would", "--", "I", "would", "like", "to", "talk", "to", "him", "first", "before", "I", "would", "comment", "on", "his", "issue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]